Hey guys, basically I came
buenos chavales básicamente me he
online today, I didn't think I'd be live
conectado hoy no pensaba ser directo
lately, every day, every
últimamente todos los días todos los
day, he also said, don't think about being live. I know
días dijo también no pensarse directo sé
that I basically came online because
que básicamente me he conectado porque
today, yesterday, I forgot to say it, but
hoy que ayer se me olvidó decirlo pero
today is the day that the
hoy es el día en el que se subía el río
Huai Hispano river was going up. Okay, you know that YouTube
huai hispano vale ya sabéis que youtube
announced that no, YouTube announced that this
anunció que no youtube anunció que este
year with everything that had happened, that there was
año con todo lo que había pasado que
a very bad year and everything else that they weren't
había es un año muy malo y demás que no
going to be the Huai Hispano river.
iban a ser el río wine vale
Okay, well, about YouTube, almost to YouTube,
a mí bueno de youtube el casi a youtube
what I really liked was the music, the
lo que me gustaba mucho era la música el
mashup, what's called the mashup that they do,
mashup que se llama el mashup que hacen
I really like it. Normally, the one they do
me gusta mucho normalmente el que hace
on YouTube last year they were recording
en youtube el año pasado estuvo grabando
a singer up close, my
una cantante de cerca me ha estropeado
cell phone microphone broke. The same thing might have happened,
el micro del móvil pueda que haya pasado
look, I'm going to record this
lo mismo mira yo voy a grabar esta
reaction. Today I'm going to do this live and I'll
reacción hoy voy a hacer este directo y
try it out a little. It's a
el poco pruebo
shame that the salsa singer isn't represented in rewind.
lástima que en rewind no se represente
You or Javi and Planas should
el salsero tú o javi y planas deberíais
appear as the greatest exponents of the year
aparecer como máximos exponentes del año
with a cameo from Turbo Plant. Apart from that, there's a
con cameo de turbo plant aparte tiene un
moment when they should remember
momento en que deberían recordar a
creators who are no longer with us.
creadores que ya no están con nosotros
Also, no  write something when you can
también que no escribe algo cuando pueda
fester I think I think
fester
you should I
creo que creo que deberías
think you should write something if you
creo que deberías escribir algo si
want to go
quiere
live or fenster okay if you
a tu el directo o fenster vale si
want to connect the live I was
quieres conectar el directo iba
commenting now everything let's
comentando ahora todo
see I imagine already seeing the cover the
a ver me imagino ya viendo la portada el
guy editing in the dick okay in case I
tío editando en la [__] vale por si se
forget to put it in the description okay
me olvida ponerlo en la descripción vale
the wine river is done by a kid
el río wine lo hace un chaval que se
named alex cool okay
llama alex molón vale
and incredible to be the same or better
e increíbles a estar igual o mejor
edited and produced than the rival himself
editado y producido que el propio rival
that I had every year okay even
que a ser yo tuve cada año vale incluso
better on many occasions okay
mejor en muchas ocasiones vale
but of course I mean already seeing the cover a little
pero claro o sea ya viendo un poco la
here what I see are
portada yo aquí lo que veo que son los
the youtubers that he likes the ones
que los youtuber que a él le gustan los
that appear okay
que salen vale
and the huaynos and by william wiley red
y los huaynos y by william wiley red
grave the cool thing here and to leave I was not going to
grave lo guay aquí y salir yo no iba a
leave Dallas nor was I going to leave
salir dallas ni iba a salir va a salir
the grave is going to leave the priest of youtube
el grave va a salir el cura de youtube
is going to leave well let's see who salas
va a salir bueno vamos a ver quién salas
more we get the surprise for good
más nos llevamos la sorpresa para bien
johann welcome welcome thank you very much
johann bienvenido bienvenido muchísimas
for that entity member today
gracias por ese ente miembro hoy
we reached 1400 okay let's see who
llegamos a 1400 vale vamos a ver quiénes
comes out
salen
last year so I like to make
el año pasado así que me gusta hacer que
me remember  roma
yo recuerde roma
roma- gallardo and tiparraco
roma- gallardo y tiparraco
okay I do
vale
n't know let's see it let's see it and give
no sé vamos a verlo vamos a verlo y
our opinion but
opinamos pero
I think a little bit of
yo creo que debería salir un poquito de
everything should be included I think a
todo yo creo que debería salir un
little bit of everything should be included okay because I think that
poquito de todo vale porque yo creo que
in the world of sanse or this year there have
en el mundo del sanse o este año ha
been very relevant things okay like
habido cosas muy relevantes vale como la
aiton gameplay
de aiton gameplay
thanks with seeing thank you very much
gracias con ver muchísimas gracias
remind everyone that you can become
recordar a todos que os podéis hacer
members for me a lot of text let this serve
miembros por mí mucho texto sirva esto
as a sincere apology
como disculpa sincera
here ten minutes talking reaching
aquí diez minutos hablando llegando a
10 minutes okay well
los 10 minutos vale
let's see it I won't go on
bueno vamos a verlo no me enrollo más
with the intro now we're increasing it
con la intro ahora lo vamos aumentando
[Music]
[Música]
of dignity of the player has exceeded the
de dignidad del jugador ha superado el
year 2020 you
año 2020
are welcome
son bienvenidos
[Music]
[Música]
a good story
un buen cuento
that supports diversity that hires and
que la apoya diversidad que contrata e
even the well I don't know if you hire the
incluso la bueno no sé si contratas a la
colleague a company that makes 3d
colega una empresa que hace 3d
animations 3d too you don't see it
animaciones 3d también no lo veis
with me you don't see it with me but in the
conmigo no lo veis conmigo pero en la
chair I don't know if it's better to react not
silla no sé si reaccionar así mejor no
if you see it like that because if not you don't see
si lo ve así porque si no no veis
some things with me there is the
algunas cosas conmigo está el perrito
little dog the meme the strong dog and the
pequeño el meme el perro fuerte y el
little dog
perro pequeño
plus
más
the pp and the  pse good grandmother but the pp
el pp y el pse buena abuela pero el pp
[Music]
[Música]
etc etc
etc etc
this I understand less I see it a lot on
este menos lo entiendo lo veo mucho en
twitter and can you explain it to me
twitter y me lo puede explicar
because he throws me off the
porque él me me eche del camello encima
tactical camel and then he puts a picture of his
táctico y luego pone una foto de la
girlfriend and they say that on top of that I do practice
novia y dicen que encima práctica hago
I've been seeing it for like two or three
yo lo llevo viendo como hará dos o tres
weeks I don't know if it was before but I don't get it have
semanas no sé si será de antes pero no
you seen how it came out and what about
habéis visto cómo salía y lo de
Javier is the best keep it up great
toma javier es el mejor sigue así grande
girlfriend I don't know tactical camel [ __ ]
novia no sé camello táctico [__]
tactical camel mother me on top of tactical
camello táctico madre me encima táctico
leave me in the comments box and you
dejarme en la caja de comentarios y
're seeing this summarized okay I want I
estáis viendo esto resumido vale quiero
want to understand all the babies I
quiero entender todos los bebés me
want to integrate into the youth I say
quiero integrar en la juventud digo
[Music]
[Música]
and this kid who is this kid
y este chaval quién es este chaval me
sounds familiar this kid could be the one with the
suena este chaval puede ser el de las
jokes
bromas
this kid I read many thanks didac
este chaval leo muchísimas gracias dídac
from Iraq rival no report the one who does the
de irak rival no report el que hace la
test hot and parish many times
prueba hot y párraco muchas veces
that this little head that is here please this
que esta cabecita que está aquí por
head what do you
esta cabeza
think it will be this little head
que creáis que será esta cabecita de
here that bonillo that appears in the meme
aquí el bonillo ese que sale en el meme
will it be the video that appears in the meme
será el vídeo ese que sale en el meme
where they cut off his hands and  he peels it
que le recortan las manos y lo pela
or rather the red-haired jota today we're going to
o sea la jota pelirrojo nos hoy vamos a
learn how to do the 07 cut
aprender a hacer el cortecito de 07
[Music]
[Música]
are you all connected
estáis todos conectados
the call of his does not spend software
la llamada de su no gasta software
Joe Roth
joe roth
here takes you to those who are
aquí os lleva a los que se están
becoming members or rather this caste are
haciendo miembros o sea esta casta son
always see they put it in the river there's algae I do
ver siempre lo meten en el río hay algas
n't know if many the 20 was the youtuber
no sé si muchos los 20 fue el youtuber
that the object in his day with the pokemon
que el objeto en su día con el pokemon
go Lopez or a lot okay and well there's
go lópez o muchísimo vale y bueno hay
an interview on my channel to spend
una entrevista en mi canal a gastar
even software there's an interview on my
hasta software hay una entrevista en mi
channel
canal
[Music]
[Música]
but suddenly it seems the guy
pero de repente por lo visto al tío se
went crazy he did very shady things there
le fue la olla hizo cosas muy turbias
are people who are the great arrested I don't know
hay gente que es el gran detenido no sé
if it's true that they arrested him not
yo si es verdad que lo detuvieron no
only did they hide it I don't know but
sólo lo ocultaron no sé pero por lo
apparently he did something [ __ ] up okay then
visto hizo cosa jodida vale luego te
here Fernando Flor with which he ends up here
aquí fernando flor con el cual acaba acá
this one will not have been updated in a couple of
este no se habrán actualizadas un par de
days no Luisito out there on a trip
días no luisito por ahí de viaje
this I don't know what this crab thing I don't
esto no sé lo que esto del cangrejo no
know add the dandy from Barcelona the
sé añadir el dandy de barcelona el baile
troll dance or the cockroach
del trole o el de cucaracha
team leader  efe team leader and 11
jefe de equipo efe jefe de equipos y 11
years old was
años
not last year
no fue el año pasado
was not last year df team the one that an
no fuera año pasado df equipo el que un
grandfather
abuelo
nacho vidal and the kid threw that I don't
nacho vidal y el chaval eché de que no
know why he risks his face and in front of
sé porque arriesga a su cara y delante
the dog
del perro
well this thing of calls in turn has
bueno esto de las llamadas de su vez ha
been very fashionable this year with this
sido muy de moda este año con esto de la
quarantine the calls of his have been the
cuarentena las llamadas de su han estado
order of the day especially in
a la orden del día sobre todo en las
classes and others do not look at the grandfather
clases y demás no mira el abuelo
free
gratis
who was this this is to someone who
quienes era ésta esta está a alguien que
made a tick tock quite ridiculous I think it is I think it
hizo un tick tock bastante ridículo creo
goes there from
es creo que va por ahí
now on
en adelante
the natives
los nativos
[Music]
[Música]
because putting this deposit
porque poner aquí a este depósito
dancing here sign interpreter sign interpreter
bailando intérprete de escena de señas
or rather putting Fernando Simn almost an
o sea poner a fernando simón casi un
icon this year for me an icon of the d I'm
icono este año para mí un icono del d
going to shut up that this good
me voy a callar que este vídeo de buen
vibes video sign interpreter as if it were this they
intérprete de señas como si fuera esto
put it of the deaf next to it and they put
lo ponen de los sordos al lado y ponen a
this deposit dancing I
este depósito bailando
don't understand I don't understand what he's
no entiendo no entiendo que se está
messing with her although
metiendo con ella aunque
because the truth and the dance seems
porque la verdad y el baile me parece
very beautiful to me
muy bonito
when there is a piece of pizza left the vivas
cuando queda un trozo de pizza las vivas
will open the carla to the oval I
abrirá la carla a la óvalo
also did an interview with her carla  to the
también le hice una entrevista carla al
water now that I remember I also
agua lo ahora que me acuerdo también
have a video with her this scale
tengo un vídeo con ella esta escala
the sister
la hermana
surely this year has entered the call
seguro que este año ha metido al llamado
more female youtubers
más youtubers chicas
because last year there were
por la cosa de que el año pasado hubo
three or four allied youtubers who said
tres o cuatro youtuber aliado que decían
that there were few women little
que había pocas mujeres poca
female representation since the truth
representación femenina ya que en verdad
is that there are fewer female youtubers in
es que hay menos mujeres youtuber en
Spain and fewer fewer women on youtube
españa y menos menos mujer en youtube
things as they are so I like it
las cosas como son
very much very well
así que me cae muy bien
my king daddy Gabi and viceroy Expsito
mi rey papi gabi y virrey expósito
my golden children
mis niños de oro
last
último
[Music] I
[Música]
don't know who this is the other one I don't know who
no sé quién es este el otro no sé quién
the pyramid is for I'll say Mario but this one I do
es la pirámide por diré mario pero este
n't know who it is
no sé quién es
oh well goodbye more finished
ah bueno adiós más terminada
how handsome the animation 2020 seemed like it was
qué guapo la animación 2020 parecía que
going to be a good year
iba a ser un buen año
[Music]
[Música]
look at
mira
this Yuki and Draw
esta yuki y draw
being here I
estar yo aquí
didn't expect it at all anyway I don't
no me lo esperaba para nada igual me da
care about this Pacheco center the bench
igual a esto pacheco centrar el banco
how strong not
qué fuerte no
all of us faced the new decade with
todos encarábamos la nueva década con
a positive attitude and I think that in the
una actitud positiva y creo que en el
car they were not even what age says I think
coche iban ni lo que dice la edad creo
until suddenly
hasta que de repente
that look the forward Arjen play
eso mira el delantero arjen play
and the other two continue that hey but  Hey,
y los otros dos seguir eso oye pero oye
but
pero
no, because I'm here until suddenly it's
no porque ser que he acá hasta que de
not because it's chemistry but instead of
no es por ser química pero en vez de
pasting there's a photo of their faces it
pegar hay una foto de sus caras no se
couldn't have been done any other way,
podría haber hecho de otra forma o sea
meaning these people would have recorded it there
que esta gente lo hubieran grabado allí
in a way that they then put it together,
de una forma que luego lo monta se
chaos began
empezó el caos
this guy has my type
este tiene mi tipo
for that kind of money
para ese tipo de dinero
I'm for ccoo the tension
estoy para ccoo no crece la tensión
between states or another person so old doesn't grow there's no
entre estados u otra persona tan mayor
no on YouTube apart from you for
no hay no en youtube aparte de ti para
whose you if North Korea
cuyo tú si corea del norte
the world will make you real in the face of a possible
el mundo te hará real ante una posible
happy holidays Javi I hope you and your
felices fiestas javi espero que tú y tu
family are having a peaceful time and
familia la estén pasando tranquilos y
are in good health happy face with
que estén bien de salud cara feliz con
smiling eyes likewise darling the
ojos sonrientes igualmente cariño el
eternal huge hug look look look
eterno abrazo enorme mira mira mira
guy look at grandpa world grandpa
tiparraco mira al abuelo abuelo mundial
[Music]
[Música]
has the one we danced to
tiene el que bailamos
in February
en febrero
several fires ravage
varios incendios arrasan los bosques de
Australia's forests destroying millions of
australia destruyendo millones de
hectares of nature
hectáreas de naturaleza
in March the pandemic due to the new
en marzo la pandemia por el nuevo
coronavirus hits the planet I
coronavirus golpea el planeta
don't like this guy the quantum
este chico no me cae bien el quantum
invoice this is a smart guy
factura este es un listillo
good repellent speaking very repellent
buen repelente hablando muy repelente
soft tom starts looking for the time
tom suave se empieza a buscar la hora
[Music]
[Música]
we are forced to be confined
nos vemos obligados a estar confinados
in our
en nuestra mirada
scarce gaze  and nobody knows how long this nightmare will last
escasas y nadie sabe cuánto durará esta
[Music]
[Música]
how not how could the cat not be here
como no como no iba a estar la gata aquí
in this little group
en este grupito
thank you very much to the oil welcome
muchísimas gracias al óleo bienvenido
the cat I I don't know how the
la gata yo yo no sé cómo se las apaña la
cat manages but the cat started on YouTube
gata pero la gata empezó en youtube hace
a year ago she doesn't have many subscribers
un año no tiene muchos suscriptores que
let's say and so many I put her I don't know how she
digamos y tantos la metía yo no sé cómo
manages
se las apaña
[Music]
[Música]
breaking news 2020 is
noticias de última hora 2020 está siendo
undoubtedly being the most chaotic year every
sin ninguna duda el año más caótico cada
week new threats are appearing
semana están apareciendo nuevas amenazas
that lead humanity the can
que conducen a la humanidad la lata
would be a little cool a little if on the
sería un poco de lo guay un poco si al
brink of extinction
borde de la extinción
the supermarkets would be
los supermercados volver a estar
collapsed again by the resource houses
colapsados por las casas de recursos
you want I
quieres
read that they invited him to turbo plant
he leído que le invitaron a turbo planta
to rewind but he had to go to the town
al rewind pero se tenía que ir al pueblo
I have to find someone I have
me tengo que buscar a alguien me tengo
to find someone next year to be in ballet half of looking for someone who knows how to edit that is the support so that he can do a ritual of the salsero of the salsero and of him he is being a king that does not appear here my fight in March with two that lasted a
mi pelea en marzo con dos que duró un
quite intense month those of aito
mes bastante intenso los de aito
gameplay
gameplay
[Music]
[Música]
all the anime joan plana you know the
todo el anime joan plana sabes la
second complaint that wants to reward me
segunda denuncia que me quiere premiar
is the one I made how cool who knows
es la que he hecho que guay quién sabe
about this story who are these people
de esta historia quién son esta gente
know if I have to the towns as many times as
sabe si tengo que los pueblos las veces
the town is the turbo plan the
que sea el pueblo el turbo plan el
jandro lion everything that would be the town
jandro lion todo lo que sería el pueblo
is I have to
sea
find someone because there are
tengo que buscarme a alguien porque hay
many who write to me ihab and I do it
muchos que me escriben ihab y yo lo hago
and then they send me sketches of the wine
y luego me mandan bocetos de los wine
that he makes me made like this made like a doll like that
que me hace hizo así hecho como muñeco
I don't want in super
yo no quiero en condiciones súper
professional conditions okay I pay someone to
profesional vale yo le pago a alguien
make me a cool king but in
que me haga un rey guay pero en
conditions of the things we have
condiciones de las cosas que hemos
lived through
vivido
who knows tax who doesn't like
quien conoce tax a quien no le mola el
toilet paper we have a vision this
papel higiénico tenemos una visión estos
is you and this is the objective
sois vosotros y este es el objetivo
prepare your weapons
preparen sus armas
come on guys
vamos muchachos
this costs this with all the leg
esto cuesta esto con toda la pata
[Music]
[Música]
the above alert
lo anterior alerta
and looking for the objective
y buscando el objetivo
here is the
aquí está
insurer objective
objetivo asegurador
the toilet paper polo of the quarantine
el papel higiénico polo de la cuarentena
for they would be the pineapple
por serían la piña
but I see how the jokes are very forced I do
pero veo como los chistes muy forzados
n't know if the same thing will happen to me I see
no sé si pasara lo mismo que a mí veo
some very forced jokes
algunos chistes muy forzados
I imagine
me imagino
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
we are not the only ones who want the
no somos los únicos que queremos el
paper
papel
we have  a good day
tenemos un buen día
only has that I don't recognize it like that
tiene sólo tiene eso no lo reconozco así
kitts and youtubers you can't see them no
kitts and youtubers no se les ve no
love
el amor
[Music]
[Música]
if it is that I already have it that's all
si está que ya lo tengo eso es todo lo
mine come on come on I already
mío
have it here and
ya lo tengo aquí y
no you do
no
n't leave me any other option
no me dejáis otra opción
marching with that flex
marchando con que flex
gloria point it
gloria punto
is very well done it is very very well
está muy bien hecho está muy muy bien
done
hecho
and ready what is the plan
y listo cuál es el plan
escape from the resale let's
escapar de la reventa
see if that phrase for the gentleman
a ver si esa frase para el señor
dear passengers liza two commanders we
estimados pasajeros liza dos comandantes
inform you that the takeoff will be
les informamos de que el despegue será
immediate please follow the
inmediato por favor sigue las
instructions of our colleagues
instrucciones de nuestros compañeros
are all in emergency
están todos en emergencia
here is
aquí
this who is paula or not she
esta está quién está la paula o no
has
esta tiene
yes no
sí no
because you have
porque tienes
friends I bet you batches with cold the
amigos te apuesto tandas con frío el
gentleman we have little fuel are you
señor nos queda poco combustible está
sure that we can wait
segura de que podremos de esperar
receive they
reciben
seem passengers and we are going to wait for them let's
parece pasajeros y vamos a esperarlos
do this point we
hagamos este punto
are going to continue
vamos a seguir
[Music] we
[Música]
recommend that you remain seated
le recomendamos que permanezcan sentados
and available the views
y disponible las vistas
under
bajo
clear how is love not going to be here to
claro como no va a estar aquí el amor
shout and again no
a gritar y otra vez no
and the one of the putting to a tip and that they don't
y el de la puesta al de un tip y que no
see tipping that they have put on the dt
vean tipping que le han puesto al dt
look at it
miralo
but today the dt has been
pero hoy el dt ha estado haciendo
exercising that because  a month ago I realized
ejercicio que porque hace un mes note
that I would have to go to the head kid
que habría que ir a cabeza chaval
[Music]
[Música]
doesn't free me from doing
no me libra de hacer
javi I can edit a video like that
javi yo te puedo editar un vídeo así
well we would have to check it out there are many
bueno habría que comprobarlo hay muchos
who have sent me sketches and the truth is
que me han mandado bocetos y la verdad
that I didn't like them
que no me han gustado
[Music]
[Música]
guys and two cameras and four we
chicos y dos cámaras y cuatro nos
matched up and it was all over listen to me
equiparamos y terminó todo
listen to me very quickly let's
escúchame escúchame muy rápido vamos a
see what I was I am on oxygen
ver que yo estaba yo estoy en oxígeno
doing and what I'm wondering these
haciendo y yo lo que me pregunto esta
people paid for done because of course some
gente pagaba hecho porque claro algunos
live in Andorra and others don't don't be
viven en andorra y otros no no sea
demanding from Andorra from Barcelona from
exigente de andorra de barcelona de
Madrid writing here a bunch of
madrid escribiendo aquí una rebujina de
people have been made they have been able to
gente se ha hecho han podido estar
travel to be able to get together and record
viajando para poder juntarse y grabar
these things and so on
estas cosas y demás
the shelter they have been recording
la protectora han estado grabando
for the last
durante los últimos
two months I don't think it was a month and a half
dos meses no creo que fue mes y medio
when the
cuando se hizo la
money collection was done not
la recolecta de dinero no
the mission of the leaves I have seen how
la misión de las hojas he visto como
literally Willy traveled for work
literalmente willy viaje por trabajo
blade
cuchilla
to the target I ran through the ship he was
al blanco he corrido por la nave estaba
about to die have you seen
a punto de morir habéis visto
no lie it's red
sin mentira es el rojo
oh
ah
and technological how long will it take for the million
y tecnológica cuánto tardará el millón
to send a message to Alex moln so that
en mandarle un mensaje a álex molón para
goal in the wine river next year
que lo meta en el río wine del año que
as he has done with a motorcycle for Pino when he has
como ha hecho con moto para pino cuando
seen thanks Morena thank you very much
ha visto gracias morena muchísimas
as he has done with a lot for
gracias como ha hecho con mucho para
Pino when when he has seen that
pino cuando cuando ha visto que
Christina and not even the pimp of the habit not to
christina y ni a el chulo del hábito no
be millions tired of criticizing the
ser millones a harta de criticar a la
motorcycle daddy saying that it clicks but
moto papi diciendo que da clic pero
now he has taken he has said it gives me crisis
ahora ha cogido ha dicho me da crise
but we are going to go and in our daddy who
pero vamos a ir y en nuestro papi que
is [ __ ] you because I am him and I did not even
está [__] te porque yo soy él y ni le
answer the message it is not that he does not
contestó el mensaje no es que no le
answer the message it is that I expose it I
contesta el mensaje es que lo expongo lo
expose it I say look at the message that
expongo digo mirar el mensaje que me ha
the chef light has sent me I expose it and I do not
mandado el chef light lo expongo y no lo
but and I do not do a collaboration
sino y no hago una colaboración por
finally he has messed with me
último se ha metido conmigo
and
y
saying
diciendo
already
ya
and
y
this is this the stick genetics' it can
esta es este el stick genetics' puede
be specific it
ser específico
can be
puede ser
[Music]
[Música]
the lack
la falta
is self-imposed his voice always no
se autoimponen su voz siempre no
Aurore does not get it Alex cool they do not
aurore no lo consigue álex molón no se
put they have to go around putting their voice
ponen tienen que andar poniendo su voz
always last year also no
siempre el año pasado también no
and does with the problems due to acids
y hace con los problemas por ácidos
were suitable are to see put you spend man
eran aptas son ver ponía gastas hombre
the one who is begging
el que está rogando
clear skirt and how could it be missing
claro falda y como podía faltar
but  of course the chlorine channel is already
pero por supuesto el canal de cloro ya
dying because it already comes out and
se está muriendo porque ya le salga y
comes out it has been a game that has hit a
salga ya sido un juego que ha pegado un
boom but a glass a huge look what
boom pero un vaso un vistazo enorme lo
the game hit for 34 weeks
que pegó el juego durante 34 semanas
but the fever has been lasting well I
pero la fiebre ha ido durando bueno yo
think the oea has been like a couple of
creo que la oea ha sido como un par de
months but it has been going down and down it
meses pero ha ido bajando y bajando ya
is already dead or rather you see the channel that
está muerto o sea tú te ves el canal de
the gold that had each video or million
que el oro que tenía cada vídeo o millón
visits in the same day when it went up
de visitas en el mismo día cuando subía
and now it has 50 to 100 thousand visits
y ahora tiene 50 a 100 mil visitas
because the gold channel
porque el canal del oro
depends on it fall guys until
depende de él fall guys hasta que salga
another game comes out and it is another a [ __ ] machine and
otro juego y sea otro una [__] máquina y
the second one also I
el segundo también
remember that I want to won the challenge
yo me acuerdo que quiero ganó el reto
of the blond
del rubios
in shape and it was the return it
en forma y era el retorno
was not a map of the blond ford night
no era un mapa del rubio ford night
is the [ __ ] master when I have always
es el [__] amo cuando siempre lo he
designed and developed an
diseñado y desarrollado una tablet panel
exclusive LED panel tablet for your channels so that you do
led exclusiva para tus canales para que
not have to put it in the sun xd how
no tengas que ponerla al sol xd como te
can I show it to you send me whatever by
la puedo mostrar mándame lo que sea por
email and you
email y tú
are seeing here the resume of his
estáis viendo aquí el currículum de su
hanger
percha
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
for  kids
para niños
[Music]
[Música]
and now it's time to get serious
y ahora es momento de ponernos serios
guys
compañeros
we've lived through one of the hardest years
hemos vivido uno de los años más duros
of our lives
de nuestras vidas
[Music] that's
[Música]
why we don't dance
por eso no bailamos
the must daddy has also gone
el mosto papi también ha ido
today no
hoy no
today we kneel before the true
hoy nos arrodillamos ante los verdaderos
heroes of this year
héroes de este año
[Music]
[Música]
the health workers
los sanitarios
and dancing
y bailar
doesn't fit at all
no pega nada
people who have given their lives for all of
personas que han dado su vida por todos
us and to all those who have left us
nosotros y a todos aquellos que nos han
their memory will live on forever
su recuerdo vivirá siempre entre
[Music]
[Música]
and having said that let's get back to the babies
y dicho esto volvamos a los bebés
the cultivation I mean I'm freaking out with the priest
el cultivo o sea yo flipo con el cura
put in put in then never one day I have to
metió metió entonces nunca un día tengo
make a video the priest is the priest he's
que hacer un vídeo el cura es el cura te
going to make a tremendous video for you one day the
va a hacerle un vídeo tremendo un día el
other day he had a thing okay and it's
otro día tuvo una movida vale y es que
a progressive priest
un cura progre
who commands 18 thousand life
quien manda 18 mil life
elena
elena
lately I've been freaking out with you lately I've
yo últimamente estoy flipando contigo
been freaking out
yo últimamente estoy flipando
thank you very much sweetheart thank you very much
muchas gracias corazón muchísimas
to me not all
gracias a mí no todos los
African descendants are a sample for you
afrodescendientes son mostró para ti
but it will be a sample daddy no
pero será mostró papi no a lo mejor hay
maybe there wasn't much daddy
que no era mucho papi
I'm making fun of a progressive priest
estoy tomando el pelo a un cura progre
yes yes yes yes he's a priest  progressives, I mean, they
sí sí sí sí es un cura progres o sea
have ideals and things, many times they
tiene ideales y cosas muchas veces y
write things that
escribe cosas
combine perfectly with the left
combinan perfectamente con la izquierda
when the left is mostly atheist,
cuando mayormente la izquierda es atea
one day this is very extensive and now I
un día esto es muy extenso y ahora me
go to interpret it and it's going to be taken out of
vaya para interpretar y se va a sacar de
context and they're going to put climb, me out there
contexto y van a poner climb yo por ahí
saying this, no, like that,
diciendo esto no así
one day, one day I will make a video
un día un día haré un vídeo bien
explaining everything and showing twist and
explicando todo y enseñando twist y
clique things about things that he has said that
clique cosas de cosas que ha dicho que
don't add up at all, you already know, but let's see
no cuadran nada ya lo sabéis pero a ver
if you are a priest, the priest, no, also, I think he is a
si eres cura el cura no además yo creo
priest but he likes them a lot, he
que es cura pero que le gusta mucho las
has read them on YouTube, I think, okay, I think that's where
ha leído de youtube yo creo vale yo creo
the Chinese are going,
que van por ahí los chinos
there are a lot of people that I know that all the people
hay mucha gente que sé que toda la gente
open their arms to him, he opens the way for him by the
le abre los brazos le abre camino por la
grace of agen, priest, a priest, a priest or whatever,
gracia de agen cura un cura un cura o
modern, to a priest on YouTube, he knows
que moderno a un cura en youtube él sabe
and they don't care or pay attention to
y no les importa ni me echan cuenta de
the things he says about the
las cosas que dice de las
contradictions or anything because since he
contradicciones ni de nada porque como
is a priest, well, let's make the joke
es cura pues vamos a hacer la gracia de
that there is a priest on YouTube, that's how
que hay un cura en youtube
people are, you know,
así son la gente ya sabéis
I am Catholic and I don't like that priest very much,
yo soy católico y ese cura no me cae muy
people who are 100% religious
bien gente que sea 100% religiosa
normally they are always putting your and
de normal siempre están poniendo tu y
saying that they don't  the priest looks good and it's
diciendo que no les quede bien el cura y
normal, I mean if you're very
es que normal o sea si tú eres muy
religious you realize things, I realized
religioso te das cuenta de las cosas yo
things, I'm a woman you know
me di cuenta de las cosas soy mujer sabe
but there are things that he says in his videos and
pero hay cosas que dice en sus vídeos y
that and they will be needed no no no I
eso y se necesitaran
want it
que no no vale quiero
one day I will have to make a video I
ya un día tendré que hacer un vídeo
will have to make a video to
tendré que hacer un vídeo para
explain it well because they are going to take
explicarlo bien porque se van a sacar
clicks out of context and they are not going to
clic de aquí de contexto y no van a
understand you know but I think he is
entender sabe pero yo creo que es
religious that he is a priest but that he
religioso que es cura pero que le gusta
really likes the YouTube jokes that being
mucho el cachondeíto de youtube que ser
famous and everything you know that one day in a
famoso y todo sabe que un día en un
video saying no it's not that the police stopped me
vídeo diciendo no es que me paro la
and the police said you are the
policía y me dijo la policía tú eres el
priest of YouTube no I mean I think he really
cura de youtube no o sea yo creo que le
likes the YouTube thing and being
gusta mucho el rollito de youtube y
famous and all that which is not
famosito y demás que no tiene nada de
bad at all it is not bad what happens is that they did not
malo no está mal lo que pasa que no
remove daddy so this is to
quitaron papá para es que esto es para
make a very long video but to
hacer un vídeo muy extenso pero para
please people you have to put
agradar a gente
very long gestures I have to
tiene que gestos muy extensos tengo que
put the clicks and things and compare it with
poner los clics y cosas y compararla con
the truth okay no there is nothing wrong with it there is nothing
la verdad vale no no tiene nada de malo
wrong but you would
no tiene nada de malo pero hay que
have to put a click to check
tendría que poner un clic para comprobar
some clicks with another  clip so
unos clics con otro clip para que lo
you understand you know that when I
entendáis ustedes saben que cuando yo
speak answer okay
hablo responda vale
you see that when I say things
ustedes ven que cuando yo digo las cosas
because I've seen things in the afternoon there's
porque he visto cosas la tarde tiene
nothing wrong with him I don't have any problem
nada de malo no tengo ningún problema
with him nor would I have challenged him to a debate or
con él ni lo hubiera retado debate ni
anything I don't like him I don't like him
nada a mí no me cae bien a mí no me cae
just okay that's it no problem
bien simplemente vale ya está no pasa
nothing happens I don't care he gets along he gets along
nada no me importa se lleva se lleva
with a lot of people no I get along I don't
bien con mucha gente no yo me llevo no
care I don't have any problem with
me importa no tengo ningún problema con
him or I mean tomorrow they invite me to
él o sea lo mismo mañana me invitan a
a game of ham that he's playing
una partida de jamón que está el juego
with or if I run into him at an event
con él o si me lo encuentro en un evento
and I happen to have a beer with him I'll have
y me tocó tomar a la cerveza con él me
it with him you know no I don't have any
la tomo con él saben no no tengo ningún
problem with him let's be clear now
problema con el que quede claro ahora
there are things that I see in his videos and
hay cosas que yo le veo en sus vídeos y
things that I see in his story they
cosas que yo le veo en su historia
distract his attitude is that it grates on me
distraen su actitud es que me chirría
simply that okay there are things that don't
simplemente eso vale hay cosas que no me
add up to me and that's it
cuadra y ya está
once where you sat
una vez donde te sentaste
[Music]
[Música]
and although later very good data crack
y aunque después muy buena data crack
but being asked gosh let's
pero siendo preguntado vaya vamos a
pay and tucumn have you
pagar y tucumán a miguel le has
asked Miguel if you never ask stupid questions
preguntado si nunca te preguntas
okay for me  that's where the [ __ ] is planet
vale para mí es donde [__] está planeta
vegetal
vegetal
how far the email show has come
qué lejos ha llegado el email show
uploading alex el capo videos
subiendo los vídeos de alex el capo
done okay
hecha vale
or so right now in the white river right now
o sea ya mismo en el río white ya mismo
in the wine river
en el río wine
we see viral clicks of tweets to the channel
vemos clic virales de tweets al canal
from the other day that stole the content to
del otro día que le robó el contenido a
steal the content from ibai and was selling his
robar el contenido a ibai y vendía su
channel he
canal
just has to
sólo tiene que hacerle un poquito la
suck up to white a little
pelotita al white
and in no time they'll be there
y en nada se ponen ahí
2020 has been full of misfortunes but
2020 ha estado lleno de desgracias pero
wait a moment
espera un momento
not all of it is bad news
no todos son malas noticias
[Music]
[Música]
will's son and seriously it's being
el hijo de will y en serio está siendo
like the lion king was going to come out there the son
como el rey león iba a salir ahí el hijo
of william I don't believe it
de william no lo creo
[Music] let's
[Música]
see I really like playing it with him
a ver me gusta muchísimo tocarlo con él
and the more I cried and especially the ones from
y cuanto más lloré y sobre todo los de
YouTube chalets less the more I'm going to play the
chalés youtube menos más voy a tocar los
young ones and more things I told them your
jóvenes y más cositas les decía vuestro
idol if all the people who are there for criticism
ídolo si dice toda la gente que hay para
criticism or cool what's happening because I
crítica crítica o cool que pasa porque
can't criticize the priest because he's a priest
no puedo criticar al cura porque es cura
or I mean you know him the one who's putting it
o sea tú lo conoces el que está poniendo
there is what I'm not going to do is the
ahí es lo que yo no voy a hacer es el
fall being and west of what's here of
fall ser y oeste de lo que hay aquí de
all good faces we all like each other very
todas buenas caras todos nos caemos muy
well and everything is very cool
bien y todo muy guay
things as they are okay I say about each
las cosas como son vale yo digo de cada
one what there is
uno lo que hay
well
bien
[Music]
[Música]
how epic this part no
qué épica esta parte no
part this part is worth millions this
esta parte esta parte vale millones esta
is the best part of the wine river and not the
es la mejor parte del río wine y no la
[ __ ] eating that we just saw
comed uría de [__] que acabamos de ver
for so long
durante tanto tiempo
[Music]
[Música]
and well this
y bueno esto
how good this
qué bueno esto
[Music]
[Música]
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
this part is the best this part seems
esta parte es la mejor esta parte parece
this part seems like one this part
esta parte parece de una esta parte
deserves to have been in a
merece haber estado en una
blockbuster
superproducción
let's see if it's a little love for children if I
a ver si es un poco amor para niños si
'm putting it in the chat but well
estoy poniendo en el chat pero bueno
listen to me it's very nice it has a lot of
escúchame que está muy guapo tiene mucha
quality that part let's
calidad esa parte
see javi I also hate
a ver javi a mí también me cagan la
most of the ones that appear in the wine river
mayoría de los que salen en el río wine
but sometimes it bothers me that they
pero a veces molesta que absolutamente
want to seize absolutely everything with controversy
todo lo quieren embargar con polémica
because your channel is wrong about the
porque tu canal está equivocado del
channel okay the channel to open
canal vale el canal de abrir huevos
kinder eggs it is called in other ways I don't
kinder se llama de otras formas no me
remember what it is called okay but this the
acuerdo cómo se llama vale pero este el
salt channel or okay the equivocal one here
canal de sal se o vale la equívoca aquí
is where the truths are told okay about
es donde se dicen las verdades vale de
each one
cada uno
but  think you're crazier than
pero piensen que son más locas que están
the kids who are suffering because I'm
sufriendo los chavales porque estoy
saying things about your idols but they're
diciendo cosas de sus ídolos pero están
here watching it
aquí viéndolo
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
5 million likes 5 million likes
5 millones de likes 5 millones de likes
is the number to enter the top 10
es la cifra para entrar en el top 10
non-musical videos with the most likes on
vídeos no musicales con más likes de
YouTube like I said this is going to be my
youtube como dije este va a ser mi
last rival so I only ask that we
último rival así que solo os pido que
make history and show once
hagamos historia y demostremos una vez
again how great our comfort is
más lo grande que es nuestra comodidad
Shoya de Colom and this has been my really cool
shoya de colom y este ha sido mi re guay
Hispanic
hispano
[Music] I
[Música]
'll be honest with you, it's not to
os voy a ser sincero ella no es por
bother you but I didn't like it
tocar los huevos pero no me ha gustado
very much
mucho
no, it didn't seem tremendous or epic to me it's
no no me apareció tremendo ni épico está
very well done okay the scenes are
muy bien hecho vale las escenas están
very well done the special effects
muy bien hechas los efectos especiales
are very well done but what has
están muy bien hechos pero lo que ha
been the story the music how they have
sido la historia la música el cómo han
connected one thing with the other and so on
conectado una cosa con la otra y demás
seemed quite weak to me it
me apareció bastante flojito me ha
seemed quite weak also it
parecido bastante flojito además me ha
seemed to me that it doesn't represent the year it
parecido que no representa el año ya
represents the year of those that you follow and
representa el año de los que tú sigues y
of how cool the little group of cool ones are  of
de lo guay del grupito de los guays de
youtube of those who got together okay it doesn't even come out there
youtube de los que nos juntamos vale ni
will be a play
sale habrá un play
and it comes out well this year I haven't done anything
y sale bueno este año no he hecho nada
relevant but I would have liked to see
relevante pero yo me hubiera gustado ver
there assault aiton gameplay with the tula
ahí asalto aiton gameplay con la tula
where implementing the tulane or that the
donde implementándose la tulane o que la
wide mining will be your
amplia minando será tu la cosas
relevant things of the year relevant things of the
relevantes del año cosas relevantes del
year okay let's see look at my face my channel is
año vale a ver mira mi cara mi canal es
a compilation kategari it bothers me that
una recopilación kategari me molesta que
in your channel of salt or wants to get out to the
en tu canal de sal se o quiera sacarse
seo and controversy and you don't believe that the king
al seo y polémica y no crees que el rey
of salsero all your col the
del salsero todas tus col
[ __ ] people
la gente [__]
to the followers of youtube
a los seguidores de youtube
these fans of u2 see how well things are
estos fans de u2 ver que bien las cosas
I would have made a mockery of the
yo hubiera hubiera hecho una burla al
touch jmr academy and of course a
toque jmr academia y por supuesto una
mockery of how pathetic that
burla de lo patético que ha sido ese
[ __ ] shitty program has been that is right the
[__] programa de [__] que atina el
program that has thrown away the money no I
programa que ha tirado el dinero no yo
would have made
hubiera hecho
a mockery okay and I would have gotten into
una burla vale y me hubiera metido con
this [ __ ] movie that was of complexion
esta [__] película que fuera de cutis
okay of course I would have put wind
vale por supuesto hubiera puesto a wind
and screaming
y gritando
and well from this date the cndh
y bien de esta fecha la cndh
to date neither the years invoices no
para fechar tampoco los años facturas no
if I had put wind and screaming I
si yo hubiera puesto wind y gritando me
[ __ ] in the [ __ ]
cago en la [__]
okay the
vale
thing about the ipads several of  put greg
lo de los ipad varios de poner a greg en
instead of having put three and put a
vez de haber puesto a tres y meterle un
bloodsucker to participate in my
chupasangre para que participe en mi
video I would have put the ipods
vídeo yo le hubiera puesto los ipod
seeing there killing people who
viendo por ahí matando a gente que
bought the ipods that's what I would have
compraba los ipod eso lo que hubiera
done okay
hecho yo vale
cabrera I don't know why they never put a
cabrera no sé por qué nunca ponen una
mockery I don't know why they don't put a mockery
burla no sé por qué no ponen una burla
of cabrera
de la cabrera
[Music]
[Música]
in progress of ry wine del salsero let's see
en curso de ry wine del salsero a ver
what comes out that I have to like
qué sale que me tiene que gustar
a lot because I would have to is a
muchísimo porque yo tendría que es una
person who says that if I once made
persona que dice que si yo le hice una
Uruguay to sauron play that he didn't
vez uruguay a sauron play que no lo
upload it and I told him the other day and I looked for it
subió y le dije el otro día y yo búscalo
because it took me a week to do it he
porque me hizo una semana hacérselo se
got on the plane and told me when he arrived
montó en el avión y me dijo cuando llegó
in rome to javi I haven't uploaded it okay
a roma a javi no lo he subido vale
and that video was the support mp a
y ese vídeo fue la apoyarse mp una
week
semana
editing the rest with a lot of love
editando lo demás con mucho cariño
fitting the scenes very well with the
encajando las escenas muy bien con la
music be I told him the other day I have
música sea le dije el otro día tengo
look for the bbc I have it in
busca a la bbc lo tengo en ordenado
old ordered I told him look what I'm going to
antiguo le dije busca lo que lo voy a
upload it to my channel it
subir a mi canal
has to be someone who edits it for me that
tiene que ser alguien que me lo edite
supports it and that represents the  year
que sea la apoya y que represente el año
relevant thing I no longer tell you the things
cosa relevante ya no te digo las cosas
of my channel but that you tell me to my
de mi canal pero que tú me digas a mi
house a rival and they take us to high of
casa un rival y nos sacan a altos de
implementing being to tula
implementando ser a tula
is not that it jumps or is relevant this year
no es que salte o es relevante este año
has been relevant clear point of
ha sido relevante punto claro de
cheap moralism and nonsense worth
moralismo barato y de tontería vale
the page of trick or we are going to is that I
la página de ardid o vamos a es que yo
would have laughed at page 2 there I do not
me hubiera reído de la página 2 ahí
know what I see that it is a rival that
no sé yo lo que veo que es un rival que
are the things that the group likes that
son las cosas que le gusta el grupo que
the little group likes the group of good that you
le gusta el grupito al grupo de bien que
give is what I see that we do not have to
das es lo que yo veo que no tenemos que
look for another person who will make a rival
buscar otra persona que hará un rival
that represents more things because the
que represente más cosas sea porque la
majority of those who are
mayoría de los que es de los
viewers here on this channel is worth the
espectadores de aquí de este canal vale
same as other channels the things that you
igual que de otros canales las cosas que
have seen there do not represent the year
habéis visto ahí no representan el año
the things that this has seen are from the
las cosas que ha visto esto son del
century that the kid has made the king
siglo que el chaval ha hecho el rey
based on what he likes
basado en lo que a él le gusta
please I am around 1.5 euros
por favor ando por el 1.5 euro
exactly
exactamente
already saw the video the town singing Cuban
ya vi el vídeo the town cantando cubana
here it has 1 m
acá tiene 1 m
if I had put other things that are
si yo hubiera puesto otras cosas que son
relevant
relevantes
I would have put the romance between
yo hubiera puesto el romance entre
skill the lollipops because we go out
habilidad las piruletas porque salgamos
dalla and I okay because I don't
dalla y yo vale porque yo no me
consider myself relevant let's see I have a much
considero relevante a ver yo tengo mucha
bigger audience
más audiencia
and a lot more relevance than some have
y mucha más relevancia que algunos han
come out there what happens is that they are the ones who are
salido ahí lo que pasa que son los que
sucking each other's [ __ ] the little
se van comiendo la pollita unos a otros
groups the forger that is here on
los grupitos el falsario que hay aquí en
youtube that I don't care about that okay but
youtube que me da igual de eso vale pero
see if you are going to be a Hispanic Uruguayan youtube
ve si tú vas a ser un youtube uruguay
you have to put things that represent a
tienes que poner cosas que represente un
little bit of everything not the cool stuff your stuff what you are is
poco todo no lo guay lo tuyo lo usted es
nothing more because for me the states
nada más porque para mí los estados
selling it all has been super viral we
vendiéndosela tula ha sido súper viral
are also mediating it the tula and the
también estamos mediando se la tula y lo
forfait crying because he was paying
del forfait llorando porque le pagaba
1.5 to I don't know who how is he not going to put that
1.5 a no sé quién como no va a poner eso
some change to Jordi's podcasts
algún cambio a los podcast de jordi
while I do
while
n't know if a debate
no sé si algún debate
but it's not a rewind and I jumped oh
pero es que no es un rewind y salcé oh
but it's that youtube is everything youtube is
pero es que youtube es todo youtube es
video games to the ceo political interview
videojuegos al ceo entrevista política
okay there I am missing politics
vale ahí me falta la política
because it is not there in the joan planas
porque no está ahí en el joan planas
l pous the plague
l pous la plaga
is that he saw things this year very
es que vio cosas este año canción muy
viral song it is very relevant but there is the
viral es muy relevante pero ahí hay lo
cool stuff the cool stuff what
guay lo guay
the blond likes and what about the
lo que le gusta al rubio y lo que tal el
l m of  show towards criticism look if
l m de show hacia crítica mira a ver si
you get it straight the m of show
os enteráis de una [__] vez el m de show
up to 50 60 thousand subscribers was a
hasta los 50 60 mil suscriptores era un
channel like the viral clips that we
canal como el de clip virales que
criticized the other day
criticamos el otro día
the md I would have made
el md yo hubiera hecho
a full version already [ __ ] once and for all and it
a versión entera ya de una [__] vez y
gets into your head okay the channels
entra en la cabeza vale los canales
these we criticize of viral clips
estos criticamos nosotros de clips
this type of channels this was the m of
este tipo de canales esto era el m de
show get it straight
show enteraros de una [__] vez
fanatics the m of excess this monetized
fanáticos el m de sobra esto monetizado
and everything is that in the field I tell him to
y todo es que al en el campo le digo que
remove it and he fought with him it's the field
lo quitase y se peleó con él es el campo
because he didn't want to remove it okay the middle
porque no lo quería quitar vale l medio
see this is called element of show
ver a esto se llama element de show
because before they were called the best of
porque antes se llamaban lo mejor de
alex the capo
alex el capo
find out well after with fifty
enteraros bien después con cincuenta
sixty thousand subscribers he started to make
sesenta mil suscriptores se puso a hacer
criticisms like we do yesterday dallas
críticas como hacemos yo ayer dallas se
started to criticize the former editor
puso a criticar al ex editor
of youtube they were missing and they put the councilor and
de youtube faltaron y ponen al edil and
field and the ones that dylan has
field y las que tiene el dylan cake
cacho dylan this relevant year
cacho el dylan este año
has found out straight that now he
se ha enterado de una [__] vez que ahora
wants to be called and I juan now that he has
se quiere llamar y yo juan ahora que se
become famous that he has the followers
ha hecho famoso que tiene los seguidores
and that  collaborates with the blond with the oven
y que colabora con el rubio con el horno
with I don't know who but find out
con no sé quién pero enteraros de una
once and for all that the medium flies this after
[__] vez que el medio vuela esto después
this was done to criticism
de esto se hizo a críticas
and up to 200,000 subscribers things and it
y hasta 200.000 suscriptores cosas y
grew with criticism
creció con críticas
find out once and for all and when it has been
enteraros de una [__] vez y cuando se ha
put on tweet and has arrived at the
puesto en tweet y se ha arribado al
blond ball I walk it they want each other there is
rubio balón lo ando se quieran allí hay
serious you are a great
grave eres un grande
now he wants to leave and yellow juan and
ahora se quiere ir y amarillo juan y lo
puts it in the play ad
mete en el anuncio de la play
and that's it you are the same your criticisms
y ya está tú eres lo mismo tus críticas
do not contribute anything and that here luciano
no aportan nada y que se aquí luciano
and what is luciano doing here
y qué hace aquí luciano
suffering I mean it is basically like that and like
sufriendo o sea es así básicamente
that one well a lot with many of those who
y como ese pues mucho con muchos de los
are there again that it is water
que están ahí otra vez que está agua por
equally it is handsome it is very well done to
igual está guapo está muy bien hecho a
me honestly I have not
mí sinceramente este año no me ha
liked how they have spun things
gustado cómo han hilado las cosas
this year to me I have not liked how the
a mí este año no me ha gustado como el
e-mail show
e-mail show
look at us the game over that
míranos el game over que le dice
the m says to him I called dallas everything and I
el m yo le llamaba de todo al dallas y
said nice things to mieres on
le decía cositas bonitas a mieres en
twitter I think he had I am not saying
twitter creo que tenía no estoy diciendo
that he pushed him or something like that
que le empujaba o algo así
look for someone on the green or see it
buscarle a alguien en el green o verlo
all his what nonsense  of post tourism and
todo suyo qué tontería de post turismo y
of well that we gave here things are
de bien que dimos aquí las cosas se
said clearly who they are
dicen claro de quién son
but well it is very well done very
pero bueno está muy bien hecho muy
good special effects very well
buenos efectos especiales muy bien
put together by story the only thing that
montado por cuento lo único que me
seems to me is that they have not represented the
parece que no han representado la movida
YouTube movement this year well for me they have not
de youtube este año pues no para mí no
represented it okay it
lo han representado vale
does an enormous job but the script
hace un trabajo enorme pero el guión a
has not fit me I have missed
mí no me ha cuadrado a mí me han faltado
many things that seemed very
muchísimas cosas que me parecían muy
relevant to many things okay a
relevantes para muchísimas cosas vale
lot of ridiculous people who have made
mucha gente ridícula que se ha hecho
viral videos as a result of the
vídeos virales a raíz de lo de la
quarantine
cuarentena
okay for example this girl who hit herself
vale por ejemplo la tía esta que se pegó
with the lamppost okay the applause on the
con la farola vale los aplausos en el
balcony the contradictions of Pedro
balcón las contradicciones de pedro
Snchez
sánchez
many things are missing what I
muchísimas cosas han faltado yo lo que
see here how good that as it is his channel
veo aquí qué bueno que como es su canal
and you can upload whatever comes out of your
y puedes subir lo que salga de los
balls and mount whatever comes out of your balls well
[__] y montar lo que le salga de los
he has made a ritual
[__] pues él ha hecho un ritual en
based on his friends
base a sus coleguitas
and stop with the nonsense stop with the
y dejarme de tontería dejarme de
nonsense from there but the thing is that the salsero
tontería de ahí pero es que el salsero
no the salsero does not look even if it is a
no el salsero no mira aunque sea una
little thing for those who are crying
cosita para los que está llorando
or it would be a little thing for the  that they are
o bien sería una cosita para los que
crying this river huai has it
están llorando este río huai lo tiene
eliminated this one hasn't been eliminated for
eliminado éste no tiene eliminado por
some reason okay
algún motivo vale
look
mira
javi being real until death
javi siendo real hasta la muerte
lollipop lollipop lollipop and that's how it
piruleta piruleta piruleta y así viene
always goes look look at this part kid in which you
siempre mira mira esta parte chaval en
are crying
los que estás llorando
those who are crying pay attention to this river
los que están llorando atento a este río
wine by alex moln in 2017 video
wine de álex molón en 2017 vídeo
deleted
eliminado
[Music]
[Música]
you have done a lot of damage objectively it
has hecho muchísimo daño objetivamente
is not true from now on for me you
no es cierto a partir de ahora para mí
cease to exist
dejas de existir
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
and it's over goodbye he's
y se acabó adiós
a little hungry too how
tiene un poco de hambre también cómo se
can you be so miserable please
puede ser tan miserable por favor
come on cepilln
vamos cepillín
why
por qué
things let's
cosas
see if I get it straight carancho we're good
a ver si me aclaro carancho estamos bien
alex volume 2017 before starting to
álex volumen 2017 antes de empezar a
get together with the cool
juntarse con lo guay
what is the river about in this of all the
de qué va el río en este de todos los
controversial topics of that year okay you
temas polémicos de ese año vale ustedes
all who are crying in the chat
todos los que están llorando en el chat
every time something happens where are
cada vez que pasa algo a dónde va a ir a
javi oliveira and dallas going to go find out about
javi oliveira y a dallas enteraros del
sanse or because all the people
sanse o porque a todas las personas les
get love or sars eo okay what's happening at
da amor o el sars eo vale que pasa por
the moment here today that wayra week michu
el momento aquí hoy que wayra week michu
no that wayra  win michu why not include it
no que wayra win michu porque no meter
this year because this
en el de este año porque en el de este
year he doesn't include the complaint about the
año no mete la denuncia que la clave del
water key and michu
agua y michu
why not include it because this year he does
porque no lo mete porque este año si se
mess with Greg about the car at 180
mete con greg con lo del coche a 180
this year if Congress did mess with it because
este año si se metía congress porque
this year Congress doesn't mess with the
este año no se mete congress con los
real headphones Angel Fall would be a little bit am and
de verdad àngel fall sería poquito am y
the fachero a little bit the hard
el facherío a poquito la comi durita de
[ __ ] food pathologies came out there to me in Far it
[__] patologías salió ahí a mi en far
would be a little bit this I am very clear
sería un poquito esto yo soy muy claro
okay and I am saying it well but if it is my
vale y lo estoy diciendo bien pero si me
turn to support I say it clearly Fall would be
toca el apoyo lo digo claro fall sería
pure and hard okay in 2017 this kid
puro y duro vale en 2017 a este chaval
thought the stories that
le parecían relevantes las historias que
are relevant the ones that everyone sees the
son relevantes las que ven todo el mundo
salseros the controversy okay but at the
los salseros la polémica vale pero en el
moment that last year he started to
momento que el otro año se empezó a
hang out with the cool ones let's see who
juntar con los guays vamos a ver quién
comes out now in 2018 life
sale ya en el 2018 vida
clear
claro
today how funny move your ass
hoy qué gracioso mueve el culo
but today from the most relevant as if it
pero hoy desde el más relevante como si
were that hour of the wine river if I
fuera esa hora del río wine si yo
control the wine river I would propose form
controla del río wine propondría forma
this and from behind at this moment it already comes
este y de atrás en este momento ya se
together  with the cool and what
junta con lo guay y qué es lo que le
happens to everyone facts when they get together with
pasa a todos hechos cuando se juntan con
the cool ones ice to the pse or caca salse or kaka
los guays ice al pse o caca salse o kaká
I the sanse or no no no no and then there's
yo el sanse o no no no no y después hay
a debate about dallas or javi oliveira it's
un debate de dallas o javi oliveira es
a debate a live saying that the
un debate un directo diciendo que la
complaint is not wanted not telling
denuncia no se quiere no contando
any [ __ ] and everyone is
cualquier movida y está todo el mundo
here but since they have to suck [ __ ]
aquí pero como tienen que chupan pollas
and it looks good then there's salse or kaka
y queda bien pues hay sal se o kaká
because he deletes a [ __ ] video because he deletes
porque borra un [__] vídeo porque borra
a [ __ ] video
un [__] vídeo
that surely would have a job okay look look look at
que seguramente tendría un currás vale
this record that you can have since it turns
este récord que te puedes tener ya que
out that I'm a terrorist and I just found out myself
resulta que soy un terrorista y me acabo
time I join the club
de enterar yo misma hora me uno al club
be successful behind stuck something is
tengas éxito atrás pegadas algo está
going on but think about the dog the two of you who are
pasando pero pensar en el perro los dos
part of the youtubers
que sois un parte de los youtubers
youtube you are a couple of people
youtube sois un par de gente
everyone who is missing a controversy in
a todo el que le falta una polémica en
2017 and it is that they are like that, I mean this whole little
el 2017 y es que son así o sea todo este
group
grupito
has deleted 600 videos due to
ha borrado 600 vídeo por tema de
copyright issues okay but this can upload
copyright vale pero este lo puede subir
because look if this one has uploaded here on
porque mira si ésta ha subido aquí en
another channel they can have it  uploaded on
otro canal lo puede tener subido el en
his channel okay has stopped all these people I've
su canal vale ha cesado todos esta gente
already said that's why I put the
ya lo he dicho por eso he puesto el
example of the e-mail show the e-mail show
ejemplo del e-mail show el e-mail show
grew uploading videos of others it was a
creció subiendo vídeos de otros fue un
channel of this of clip
canal de esto de clip
then it was a channel of criticism that
luego fue un canal de críticas que
comments on everything like the e-mail
comenta todo como el e-mail
made a video even of win michu irala
hizo un vídeo hasta de win michu irala
are you telling me I made a video
me estás contando hice un vídeo
defending me har
defendiendo a me haré
and criticizing arrese and criticizing this one I think he
y criticando arrese y criticando a este
also criticized him he found
creo que también lo critico ha hallado
that I opened a bs account what the [ __ ]
que abriera una cuenta de bs que [__] me
are you telling me man
estáis contando tío
are you telling me that sanse
me estáis contando a mí de que el sanse
or not that it is that these people do not like
o no de que es que esa gente no le gusta
controversy what happens is that now it
la polémica lo que pasa que son ahora
suits us well because they are where they are
nos bien queda porque están donde están
now hanging out with whoever is but for
ahora juntándose con quienes están
me stop touching my dick I
pero a mí dejarme de tocarme la [__] yo
say things as they are
digo las cosas como son
I say things as they are and things
yo digo las cosas como son y las cosas
are that to me the guaipo river more lacking
son que a mí el río guaipo más faltado
for the truth things the tula the town
por las cosas de verdad la tula the town
shaking around there to drone the catch
meneándose por ahí a drone la pillada
we made with the page of ardid or the
que hicimos con la página de ardid o el
joan plana
joan plana
totally put the president of the
puesto totalmente el presidente del
government and  Pablo Iglesias
gobierno y pablo iglesia expuesto
fully exposed what happens is that most of
totalmente lo que pasa que la mayoría de
those people are little poems
los de de los de esa gente son poemitas
and they are not going to mess with Pablo Iglesias he
y no van a meterse con pablo iglesia
is being reported
está denunciado
a lot of things for throwing him many
un montón de cosas por echarle muchas
thanks missing a ton of things in
gracias a falta un montonazo de cosas en
that rival that they have put in the rival that you
ese rival que han metido en el rival que
have said video game in hand
habéis dicho videojuego en la mano el
love the fall gay
amor el fall gay
schapces uruguay season riva in 2017 with
schapces uruguay season riva en 2017 con
all these controversies because in
todas estas polémicas porque en el de
this year's he has not put that the UNR
este año no ha metido que la unr
has been sentenced to 40 thousand turkeys because
ha sido condenada a 40 mil pavos porque
you already like it with the cool you are no longer
ya te gusta con lo guay ya no te
interested in the salsa singer I do not see it hidden
interesa el salsero no lo veo escondida
yes secretly and I see it the sanse or
eso si a escondidas y lo veo el sanse o
but for Higuain or Paraguay he calls me the
pero por higuain o paraguay me llama al
priest and this one and the other one goes and
cura y al de este y al otro anda y las
sucks the top ones really is that to me the
chupas las top de verdad es que a mí el
serious fall man to me the serious fall and the
fall serio tío a mi el fall serio y el
noir facing
noir de cara
me the fall would be and not going face to face you do not
a mí el fall sería y el no ir de cara no
know how it touches my balls I
sabéis cómo me toca las pelotas de
really say it you do not know how all my
verdad lo digo no sabéis cómo me todas
balls and I say it is very good it is
las pelotas y lo digo está muy bien está
very very  well put together, a lot of work, it also
muy muy bien montado mucho curro también
has a production of the option because it has
tiene una producción de la opciã porque
asked, it has done, I don't know if two or three
ha pedido ha hecho no sé si dos o tres
direct raising money
directo recaudando dinero
and I don't know how much it raised but a few
y no sé cuánto recaudo pero unos cuantos
thousand no,
de miles no
anyway, the video is very good, it is
en fin que está muy bien el vídeo que
very well put together, it is very well done,
está muy bien montado que está muy bien
everything is super detailed, whatever you
hecho todo que está súper detallista lo
want is fine, but for me it was missing,
que queráis vale pero a mí me ha faltado
apart from the fact that I didn't like how
aparte de que no me ha gustado cómo ha
the music was done, the mashup is fine, I didn't
estado hecho la música el mashup vale no
like it, I didn't like
me ha gustado no me ha gustado tampoco
how the connections from one theme to
cómo han ido las conexiones de un tema a
another went, okay, more, something relevant is missing, that's it
otro vale más falta cosa relevante